Though, my friends and welcome to exercise number 35 in this exercise, we are asked to find the common
elements between the two, right?
So we need to make any program or algorithm that find the common elements between two areas.
We have to erase entries.
So we are taking an interest in order to make the coding simple.
And we need that the algorithm, that concept to be understand, OK, understood correctly.
So.
Both the video and think about it, how to find that come in that common between that and other they
want and as they do.
So I am waiting.
Your solution, guys.
So in order to may maybe discuss anything, maybe maybe I could help you in understanding ways better
if I see your code.
So please comment below in order to see your way of thinking your algorithm, your.
Your way of driving records, OK?
These are the elements of element of the array to and this element elements of array one.
So.
We start by comparing this element, we took an element here, I'm I'm showing you how we make that
algorithm work.
OK, so we start to compare the first element with elements of the second array.
OK.
So comparing this?
Would result in an array, so if we took no one and we need to compare it with these numbers when we
need to put it inside an array and it looks pretty to compare these elements.
Now, if I need one element to compare with these elements, I need one look.
But if I need at loop.
Or that goes through all the elements and compare these elements to that to these elements.
Also, I need to make a another loop, so I need a loop to compare the elements and I need an outer
loop that go through the elements and compare them.
Correct.
OK.
So one for movie one.
One loop to move from one element to another.
And I need a nested loop that goes through the elements and compared them with the elements of Array
two.
OK.
You understand the concept, guys.
This is very important.
So this loop outer loop will go through these elements and the inner loop will go through these elements.
So how to make this happens?
We start by making an outer Lou Ford
and I equal to zero I less than our way one goes.
This outer loop will go through this element, so I need to go through the elements of array one.
OK, so that length five plus plus and I need to go inside this loop, another loop that contains this
number that took an element and compared it with the whole numbers.
OK.
So the algorithms tell us to do can element from here and compare it with all the elements, then move
to the next element and compare it with all the elements.
The third, compare it with the all elements five and so on.
OK.
In order to do that, I told you in the previous video and to make an institute.
And in this video also the same concept, but different syntax came out of the two dot length.
I'm comparing all elements of of the second array.
And start to compare if Array one Appendix II equal
that they do at Index J.
Then.
If then, sorry.
Yes, I need to remove the spaces.
Then tell me that system that the print, that this common elements are current and
common element.
Plus.
Every one at index.
Oh, okay.
It's very simple.
OK, now let's run and see the common elements, the common element is four, yes, four and four.
Five.
Here five and here five and seven.
Here seven and a to contain seven.
OK, so this is the algorithm in order to find the common elements between.